

### IRYNA SKARAIEVA

## **Front-End Developer**

I'm a Front-End Developer transitioning into IT after many years of working in education. My teaching experience has equipped me with strong analytical skills, problem-solving abilities, and teamwork capabilities. With a foundation in JavaScript, React and HTML/CSS, I focus on crafting functional, visually appealing web applications to enhance user experiences.

Proposals for cooperation with technologies that need to be studied are welcome!

#### **CONTACT DETAILS**

+421919495444

Trnava, Slovak Republic

#### LINKS TO OTHER RESOURCES

<u>Portfolio</u> WhatsApp Telegram

<u>Linkedin</u> <u>Facebook</u> <u>GitHub</u>

#### **SKILLS**

**HTML** 

CSS

**JavaScript** 

**SCSS** 

React

Next.js

**Figma** 

Bulma

**Tailwind CSS** 

LANGUAGES

**Native** 

C2

**B1** 

R1

Ukrainian

Russian

**Enalish** 

Slovak

# WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Private Tutor**

Self-Employed, Remote, UA, SK | Feb 2020 - Mar 2024

- · Managed the educational process for a home-schooled student.
- · Provided individual tutoring in mathematics, tailored to the unique needs and learning styles.
- · Individual preparation for exams.

#### **Content Manager**

Freelance, Vinnytsya, UA | Feb 2016 - May 2017

- · Editing and managing website content using the Content Management System.
- ·Strict compliance with requirements and deadlines.

#### **Teacher of Physics and Astronomy**

Medical College, Mykolayiv, UA | Jan 2014 - Aug 2015 Secondary School, Odesa, UA | Sep 2007 - Sep 2012

- · Created educational materials, building skills in multimedia.
- · Developed instructional documentation.
- · Supervised student groups.

#### Accountant

T&T, Mykolayiv, UA | Jan 2013 - Mar 2013

- · Processed financial transactions with accuracy and attention to detail, managed large datasets, enhancing analytical skills.
- · Adapted to new software, proving flexibility and fast learning.

## DRIVING LICENSE

В

#### **EDUCATION**

#### The Faculty of Physics and Mathematics

Teacher of Physics, Computer Science and Life Safety Basics **Master's degree** Sep 2002 — June 2007

South Ukrainian National Pedagogical University named after K. D. Ushynsky